[{"answer": "Okay, now hold this card up to the crowd. Was that the card you picked", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Four of hearts? Really? Look again", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm not really happy", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "My potential hasn't even been reached", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I don't care! I'm leaving!  'Scuse me", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm going home", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Where are you going", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You don't want to go home", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm not in the way. You are. Are you unhappy with the Church's teachings? Let's just talk about i", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Why don't we go into the back room for a second, and talk? Then you can leave", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Come on, my friend, this is stupid", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "A part of what?! Some gaywad magician's crazy life plan?", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Don't call Mr. my friend a gaywad! He's a brlliant ma", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm not going anywhere", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No, they just convinced you that he's a brilliant man! Let's go", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Goddamnit, I'm not going with you! I wanna stay here", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Then I guess... I'm a dumbass", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Well, this is what I believe in now, my friend. And if you can't respectr that,... then I guess we're not best friends anymore", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Then what are we going to do", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Super best friends", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "That's right, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Uh that's what I said. Sea Man", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "South-Park-The-Super-Best-Friends.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "...Um... Let me think, um... a giant stone my friend", "qsentId": 24}]